icelandreview.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy and Cookie policy – Iceland Review

### **Effective Date:   August 1, 2018**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Iceland Review and our website; http://www.icelandreview.com **.**  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:

  * What information we collect;
  * With whom it is shared;
  * How it can be corrected;
  * How it is secured;
  * How policy changes will be communicated; and
  * How to address concerns over misuse of personal data.

## **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship and deliver the magazine.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new services or changes to this privacy policy.

## **Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address provided on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

## **Registration for Iceland Review Subscribers**

In order to use this website to access Iceland Review magazine archives, users must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address, etc.). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

## **Iceland Review Subscription**

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

All the billing information is processed through Sales Cloud who have their own Privacy and cookie policy here: <https://www.salescloud.is/privacy>

## **Sharing**

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## **Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

## **Cookies**

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

## **Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## **Notification of Changes**

If we change our Policy, we will post the changes on this page. Please check the website regularly for any changes to this Policy. However, from 25 May 2018 any significant changes will be provided to you directly where possible.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via** **  email at icelandreview@icelandreview.com.**
